betdsi.eu 2018-11-09

# Website Privacy Policy | BetDSI

BetDSI considers your privacy one of our utmost concerns. This Privacy Notice outlines our current policies and practices regarding how information about individual customers is collected and used. We will send existing customers an updated Privacy Notice on an annual basis.

In order to provide you with individualized service, BetDSI collects information about you from your account application and other forms that you may deliver to us. This information includes, but is not limited to, name, address, email address, phone number, nationality. BetDSI also collects information about your transactions with BetDSI and its affiliates. We use this information to open an account for you, process your requests and transactions and to provide you with additional information about our products and services.

We safeguard the confidentiality of your information in a number of ways. For example:

  * **BetDSI** does not sell or license lists of our customers or the personal, non-public information that you provide to us.
  * **BetDSI** restricts access to the personal, non-public information that you have shared with us to and is limited to our employees, agents, and affiliates who need to know such information in connection with the services that we provide to you.
  * **BetDSI** maintains strict employment policies that prohibit employees who have access to your personal, non-public information from using or disclosing such information except for business purposes.
  * **BetDSI** takes substantial precautions to safeguard your personal, nonpublic information. For example, the BetDSI’s system can be accessed only by authorized personnel via valid user names and passwords. In addition, our Internet-based systems include security measures such as encryption and firewalls. BetDSI uses the personal, nonpublic information that we collect from you to service your account (e.g., to qualify you for using the services available through the BetDSI system and to execute and confirm your BetDSI transactions). In doing so, we may share such information with our employees, agents, and affiliates.

By using our services, you agree to receive updates on promotions, sporting events, account activities, and transactional receipts via email, push notifications, SMS messaging. However, we will NEVER spam you nor distribute your information to any 3rd party. If a request by a member is made to add third party tools such as wager trackers or other technological services and apps that connect your account to that third party service, we will only use the data required to assist with your requested connection.

We do not disclose any nonpublic personal information about our customers to other independent firms, organizations or individuals except in furtherance of our business relationship with you, or as otherwise permitted or required by law. For example, among other reasons we may disclose or report such information: where necessary to authorize, effect, administer, or enforce transactions that you request or authorize; to maintain and administer your account; to provide you with account confirmations, statements and records; to maintain appropriate archival records; where we believe that disclosure is required by applicable law, rules or regulations; to cooperate with law enforcement or regulatory or self-regulatory organizations; to enforce our customer and other agreements; to meet our obligations, or to protect our rights and property.

If you decide at some point to close your BetDSI account, we will continue to adhere to the privacy policies and practices described in this notice.

We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with federal standards to guard your personal information.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding the privacy of your information at BetDSI, please contact us to [CSD@betdsi.com](mailto:csd@betdsi.com) or via our [Live Chat](https://www.betdsi.eu/contact/).
